Hello Namaskar friends, welcome to
our youtube2 info friends, today we are going to
talk
about the top five shares whose returns have gone high and low,
friends let's start with
five gainer shares whose returns have gone
high, which have performed well, we will
inform you about them,
so let's start
from the first number, friends
our number one share is Doctor Redis Laboz
Limited, friends if we talk about its share price, then
its share price
is
5590 and 50 paise, friends its share price
is Doctor Redis Laboz Limited,
friends talk about its returns, as you
can see, if we talk about its returns, then the
return it has given
in one day, friends it has
given a return of 2.97,
so friends the increase in it is
161 and there has been an increase of 4 paise
in this share, if friends we look at its graph five days
ago, then five days ago
instead of negative, it had performed, so
friends 5 days ago  There was a jump of 2.16,
so today also it has performed well, it has
given a return of 2.97 in a day, if
friends you have a holding in it then
you can sell your shares and
take your profit, this is a good opportunity to
invest and withdraw money in it, so this was
our number one share, now let's go
friends, the second number share is
our Mutu Finance, friends, let's
talk about its share price, its current share is 23,
friends, its current share price is 23, friends, talking about Mutu
Finance,
friends, today's return, it has given a
return, so it has given
friends,
it has given a high return of 3.1, so
at 3.15 it has a high return today
and its money has increased, then
it has increased by 825 paise, friends,
so this is a good opportunity if you have a
holding in it, so
if you have invested money in Mut Finance Limited, then
you can sell your shares and your  You
can take out profit
if friends talk about its five days ago, then
5 days ago there was a jump in it, then
5 days ago there was a
fall of 0.76 in it, so today is a good opportunity to
sell your shares in it,
friends, if you have a holding in it, then
now friends let's move towards the next share, the
next share is
our Ro Motors
Corporation, friends Ro Motors, this is our share, if we
talk about its share price, then its
share price you can see is
354.50 paise, friends its stock price is,
so today the jump in it has come,
friends, it has
jumped by 2.85 or there has been an
increase of 2.85, if we talk about
this money, there is a increase in it and friends, there has been an increase of
50 paise in it,
then friends, if we
take out the details of its five days ago, then the increase in it five days ago was
2.12
and if we take out its chart of one day and one month, then
friends, there has been an increase of 3.79 in it since one month ago, that is,
this share  It is continuously
increasing, so
friends,
if you have a holding in it right now, then do
not sell your shares right now because
now is the opportunity, this stock is about to run further,
so do not sell your stock right now,
maintain some patience,
we will soon tell you
when you can sell your shares because it is Ro Motors
Corporation, friends, now it is going to sell a lot during the festival time
because Ro Motors manufactures, it is a
motorcycle company, so friends, there will be
sales in motorcycles now
because now the time of Diwali is about to come, so
friends, many of our people also
buy and take out their vehicles only on Diwali, so
now it will increase further, so right now
if you have a holding in it, then
hold your shares and
in the coming few months
you will see a good profit in it, so
friends, this was our second number
share, now friends, let's move towards the next share, friends, the next share is
our
Jinal Steels and Powers, friends, let's
talk about its
share price, its share price is
72, friends, its per annum, let's talk about
its returns, friends, it made returns today  If it has been
given then it has been given friends, it has
given a return at 2 p.96 or
friends the increase in it is 20 and
p. So it is a good opportunity
friends if you have a holding in it
then you can sell your shares
and take your profit
friends if we see its chart of five days ago
then 5 days ago also it has
increased by 2 points at 2 p.18
in the share and if we see the chart of one month then the
fall in it in one month was
0.74 p. So
friends it is a good opportunity if
you have a holding in it then you
can sell your shares and take your profit
now friends let's move
towards the next share next share is
our ICICI Comms friends
ICICI Comms General Insurance
Corporation Limited friends let's talk about its
price then its share price is
304 friends its share price so the
return it has given today is given
friends
it has given a return at 2 p.30.33 or
it has made a return at 2.33  It is given that today
it has increased by
399 and 75 paise, friends, there has been an increase in it, so
friends, if
we talk about ICI covers according to its chart, if we
look at the chart of 5 days ago, then it has
declined, five days ago friends, the share had
declined and today it has jumped, so
friends, this is a good opportunity for you, if
you have a holding in it, if you have
sold this share or bought it, then
you can sell your share and
take your profit, we will keep you
informed and will keep giving you information like this, for this
you
should subscribe to the channel and
like the video so that you can
get notifications of the videos posted by us,
now let's go to the next share,
our last share which is our fifth number, that is
Jio
Financial Services, friends, Jio Finance
Services
Limited, in this share, friends, if we
talk about its share price, then the current share price is
21, its share price is Jio
Financial Services Limited, if friends,
talk about its returns, then as
you can see, the returns it has made  If it has
given, then it has given
friends by giving a return of 2.64, that
is, it has given a return of 2.64, the
increase in it, friends, has
increased by 95 paise, if we
look at its chart of five days ago, then the increase
in it, five days ago, was
at 0.52, that is, the
jump in it today, it has
jumped well, so you can sell your shares
and take your profit,
we will keep informing you like this and keep giving you
information, for this
you can visit our
YouTube channel, in which there has been a lot of decline
and we will discuss about those shares, so
let's start friends,
from the first number, our number one share
is
friends HCL
Technology, friends, if we talk friends about its
share price, then its share price is
as you can see, friends,
its share price is 1237, friends, the
fall in it has happened today,
friends, there has been a fall of 0.39, so
friends, this is a good share,
you also have a good opportunity to invest in it, if you want, then  You
can invest money and buy this share
because this share is going to
jump in the coming time. If we
talk about its maximum, friends,
as you can see, the
graph has gone up in the maximum chart. If
you hold it for a long time, then
you can make a good profit. So, according to
my suggestion, you should invest
money in this share
and earn money. Now let's move
towards the next share. The next share is
our
Tech Mahindra.
Friends, if we talk about its share price, then its
share price is 0.2. Friends, its SEQ is 0.37. So, the
decline in its returns has
come,
friends, it has fallen to 0.37.
Friends, there has not been much decline in it. So,
you should not buy the share right now because
when a good opportunity comes, we will inform you, then you
can buy this share, but right now is
not a good time to invest money in this share.
Yes friends, now let's move towards the next share. The
next share is our third number
Adani Bill Mar, friends, Adani Bill Mar
Limited, Adani Bill Mar Limited. If we
Friends, if we talk about its share price, then
its share is worth 37 in the share price, 337 and
its share is worth 10 paise and if we talk about the return, then
it has
made a negative return of 0.50, so
friends, this share is cheap but you should
not invest money in it right now because it has
not fallen much, it has
fallen by 0.50, if friends, if you look at the chart of this 5 days ago, then it was
falling five days ago as well,
so this share saw a huge jump,
as you can see,
what is going on in it right now, friends, it is falling, or
you can see that there is a decline,
so according to my advice,
friends, you should not invest money in this share
because your money can be lost and we do not
want your money to be lost, so you should
not invest money in it, now friends, let's move
towards the next share, the next share is
our Aion Paint, friends, Aion
Paint
is such a good share, if you want, you
can invest money in it, this is a good opportunity to invest money in it, if we
talk about its price, then
friends, its price is running at ₹10 and ₹
366, it is running at ₹10  The fall that has happened in this is of
0.14, so this is a good
opportunity to invest in it.
If you want to invest money in this share, then always
invest in the falling part and not on the
rising part. Friends, if we
talk about the maximum, then this share is going to go up in the long run.
If you invest money in it in the long run, then
you will only get
profit and not loss and we will
not let you suffer any loss. If you
watch our video, then you will not have to face any loss.
For this, you can watch our
youtube1 video. Till then,
Ram Ram to all friends.